disk.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | Corporate Disk Company - Disk.com

Corporate Disk Company strongly believes in protecting your privacy while providing you with exceptional service.  
Here is an explanation of our privacy policy and how we safeguard the personal information provided to us on our Web site.

### **Information Collection**

When you visit Corporate Disk’s Web site, we do not collect personal information. We do log your IP address, which allows us to review which parts of our website you visited and how much time you spend there. This type of information helps us to improve our website to better meet your needs. We do not use your IP address for anything that can be used to personally identify you. Unless you register on our site, we do not know your personal identity.

Like most websites, Corporate Disk’s website uses Internet cookies which are small files that are placed on your hard disk for record-keeping purposes only. We use cookies for two purposes: to determine who is a repeat user and to measure usage patterns to help us to improve our website.

Please be aware that our privacy policies apply only to Corporate Disk’s website and are not applicable to any other website; including those that are linked to our website. We encourage you to learn about the privacy practices of any website you visit.

### **Information Use**

We do not share personal information with outside parties. Corporate Disk Company does not sell, rent, or lease your email, name, address or any other personal information to others with or without your consent. Aggregated data that does not include personally identifiable information is used to improve our website and customer service and communications and may be shared with others.

We do not partner with or have special relationships with any spammers or ad server companies. Actually we truly despise spammers just as much as you do.

We do send email updates on the latest Corporate Disk Company products, special promotions, and newsletters to those people that have opted online to receive such information.

### **Email**

All email offers from Corporate Disk Company will tell you how to decline further emails. At any time, you may request to discontinue receiving these offers from us by emailing us at [info@disk.com](mailto:info@disk.com). Please provide us with the specific email address you want to opt out. If you don’t you know we will screw it up.

### **Data Security**

Corporate Disk Company uses appropriate security measures to assure that your personal and credit information is kept completely confidential. There is no external access to this information and its internal access is highly limited and strictly monitored.

Corporate Disk Company’s privacy policy is subject to change at any time. Corporate Disk Company will provide notice 30 days prior to implementing any major changes to our privacy policy by posting such changes to our website.

##### If you have any question specific to privacy
